{
    "subject": "resource/Michael_Collins_(astronaut)",
    "predicate": "ontology/nationality",
    "object": "resource/United_States",
    "human_readable": "Michael Collins (astronaut) is from United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.738650918006897,
            "question": "Where is Michael Collins from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5331689715385437,
            "question": "What is Michael Collins known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5006749033927917,
            "question": "What country was Michael Collins born in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4920218288898468,
            "question": "Is Michael Collins associated with a specific space mission?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4878136217594147,
            "question": "When was Michael Collins born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4647112190723419,
            "question": "Did Michael Collins travel to space?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.33440494537353516,
            "question": "Was Michael Collins a pilot?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24305832386016846,
            "question": "What was Michael Collins' role during his missions?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.18638117611408234,
            "question": "Did Michael Collins participate in any lunar landings?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.15221863985061646,
            "question": "Has Michael Collins been awarded any medals or honors?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Michael Collins (astronaut) is from United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7071_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Did Michael Collins participate in any lunar landings?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7071_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was Michael Collins' role during his missions?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7071_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was Michael Collins a pilot?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7071_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7071_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7071_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7071_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7071_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7071_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7071_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7071_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7071_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7071_9.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7071_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because all four documents contain information that confirms Michael Collins was an American astronaut, and specifically states that he was born in Rome, Italy (which is a country in Europe) and later became a U.S. citizen and worked for NASA as part of the U.S. space program."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide multiple references to Michael Collins being an American astronaut, including his birthplace in Rome, Italy, and his selection as part of the third group of fourteen astronauts in 1963. These details support the statement that Michael Collins is from the United States."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}